tendertiger.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy : www.TenderTiger.com

|  **E-Procurement Technologies Limited (ETPL),** the owner of this website, has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our deep commitment to the privacy of our site, visitors and customers. As a company, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines and we continually review our policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of our visitor and customer information. We request all the users of our website to go through this policy to understand how their personal & business information will be treated as they make full use of our services to their benefit. 

The visitors are requested to note that this policy is applicable to the market-place operated by ETPL only and any link which is provided to re-direct the visitor to any other application outside ETPL but which could prove beneficial to the visitor, but the information for which we are not accountable. 

Following is an explanation of our commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet Users of our application 

This privacy policy applies to all the publicly accessible pages on [www.TenderTiger.com](http://www.tendertiger.com/). Responsibility for the privacy policies or practices of third party sites, linked to [www.TenderTiger.com](http://www.tendertiger.com/) is beyond its control and we do not guarantee of any damage whatsoever for that.   
  
---  
Information Collection   
In accordance with the Guidelines, the website collects and uses the following information in Tendertiger.com: 

1\. System information   
2\. Personal and organizational information   
3\. Tender notification information.   
  
System Information   
For each page you access on the www.Tendertiger.com site, information that identifies the following is recorded: 

• IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer system which has accessed it   
• Top-level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc.)   
• Address of your server   
• Date and time of your visit to the site   
• Pages accessed and documents downloaded   
• Previous website visited   
• Type of browser and operating system you have used. 

The information collected during each visit is combined to produce reports in order to identify patterns of usage of our website which is very instrumental to us in terms of understanding the requirements of the visitors in general and thus improving the quality of our application by being more user-friendly and also enhancing the services offered on it. We will not disclose or publish information that identifies individual machines, or potentially identifies sub-groupings of addresses, without consent or otherwise in accordance with the 

_IT ACT 2000_  
Personal and Company Information   
When you become a registered user of our website you are asked to provide the following information, some of which (those marked with *) are mandatory: 

• Email Address *  
• Password *  
• First Name *  
• Last Name *   
• Organization\Company Name *  
• Street Address   
• Town/City  
• State/Territory *  
• Postcode *   
• Country *  
• Phone Number *   
• Fax Number  
• Mobile Number

This information is used to identify those who have registered on Tendertiger.com website. The system records this information for the business of tendering purpose only. The information is not used for any purpose other than tendering related matters or the support of registrants in the use of Tendertiger.com website. Users are responsible for keeping their contact information current so that they do not miss out on any important tender lead form Tendertiger.com. The information collected is never ever passed to any third party or company and the information is strictly kept confidential. The Tendertiger.com will not add email addresses to any mailing lists or disclose email addresses for other purposes without the owner's prior consent by way of a specific request in writing.   
  
Cookies:  
Tendertiger.com uses a cookie to maintain contact through a session. The cookie allows Tendertiger.com to recognize you as an individual as you move from one page of the website to another. The cookie will expire when the browser session is closed or the computer is shut down. No attempt will be made to identify anonymous users or their browsing activities unless legally compelled to do so, such as in the event of an investigation.   
Links:  
The Site contains links to other web sites and resources. Independent third parties provide these sites and TenderTiger.com is not responsible and shall not be liable for the availability or content of these outside resources.  
Log Files:  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track site use, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
Security of Stored Information:  
This website takes every precaution to protect our user’s information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best available encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices in accordance with ISO 27001:2005.
